<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>HalfBlog</title>
    <link href="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog" />
    <updated>2025-08-11T09:54:12+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>MrHalfLife</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog</id>

    <entry>
        <title>The internet is replacing parents.</title>
        <author>
            <name>MrHalfLife</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/the-internet-is-replacing-parents.html"/>
        <id>https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/the-internet-is-replacing-parents.html</id>

        <updated>2025-08-02T13:12:24+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    So, if you haven’t heard, a lot of things are changing in English-speaking countries. The US, UK, and Australia have implemented, or are about to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p data-start="94" data-end="349">So, if you haven’t heard, a lot of things are changing in English-speaking countries. The US, UK, and Australia have implemented, or are about to implement, laws to “protect kids.” It’s disguised as protecting kids, but it’s actually about mass control.</p>
<p data-start="351" data-end="773">In my opinion, this is dumb. If you live in the UK, you must prove you’re 18 or older with either a government ID (like a driver’s license) or a face scan, which is creepy as fuck. Where is this data stored? I don’t know. What if it’s on a system from 1999 set up by people who know nothing about basic cybersecurity? If I were a UK citizen right now, I’d be worried about what happens to my data once I send it to them.</p>
<p data-start="775" data-end="922">The UK government has told people “don’t share your driver’s license online,” yet they’ve implemented a law that basically forces you to do that.</p>
<p data-start="924" data-end="1415">They’ve even restricted Spotify. Are we deadass? How can swear words or some other shit be considered dangerous for youth? For example, Lounge Act by Nirvana is marked explicit because of the line “I’ll keep fightin’ jealousy / Until it’s fucking gone,” which shouldn’t be considered explicit in the first place. The UK government acts like those weird Christians who say “if you swear, you’ve sinned.” For some reason, Nirvana’s song Rape Me isn’t marked explicit, and I have no idea why.</p>
<p data-start="1417" data-end="1723">Why should the government even act like the parent here? Parents might know a lot about the internet and can restrict usage themselves. This is like when a parent isn’t watching their kid, the kid touches the stove and gets burned, and then the parent sues the stove company for not making it “kid safe.”</p>
<p data-start="1725" data-end="1897">The Australian government is doing the same thing. They literally ban all social media for anyone under 16. Could kids still be anonymous online? Maybe, but I don’t know.</p>
<p data-start="1899" data-end="2042">This might change in the coming months if the European Parliament decides to push the same thing happening in the UK. Let’s see what happens.</p>
<p data-start="2044" data-end="2403">Lastly, YouTube is rolling out a US-only feature that guesses your age based on your watch history. In true Google fashion, they use AI to do it. If the AI is wrong, you must submit your ID to Google. TikTok is also adding age verification for US users if they think you’re underage. So if I get Italian brainrot on my For You Page, does TikTok think I’m 5?</p>
<p data-start="2405" data-end="2575">Right now, this is only for US users, and it’s unknown if Google or TikTok will do the same in Europe. At this point, we should all be living in Eastern Europe or Asia.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>ts pmo (adblocker blockers)</title>
        <author>
            <name>MrHalfLife</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/ts-pmo-adblocker-blockers.html"/>
        <id>https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/ts-pmo-adblocker-blockers.html</id>

        <updated>2025-06-15T15:52:17+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hello, So, YouTube is trying to shame you for using an adblocker, just to push you into buying YouTube Premium. They're deliberately making the platform&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><strong>Hello,</strong></p>
<p data-start="78" data-end="694">So, YouTube is trying to shame you for using an adblocker, just to push you into buying YouTube Premium. They're deliberately making the platform experience worse, showing messages like "Experiencing issues?" when loading a video. If you click "Find out more," it simply blames ad-blocking extensions, saying something along the lines of:<br data-start="416" data-end="419"><em data-start="419" data-end="626">"Yeah, these extensions that block ads are the reason why. They were made with evil intentions to ruin your video experience. Just disable them and you'll be happy, without that thing that came from hell."</em><br data-start="626" data-end="629">Like, what? They’re literally shaming you for using an adblocker.</p>
<p data-start="696" data-end="1006"><strong data-start="696" data-end="711">My opinion:</strong> YouTube needs to chill and admit they’re degrading the experience for adblock users on purpose. And let’s be honest, adblockers are great. I bet someone at Google uses one. The internet is practically unusable without one. Go to any major news website with an adblocker turned off, it’s a complete mess.</p>
<p data-start="1008" data-end="1259">I really wish governments would implement proper ad regulations, making it illegal for websites to intentionally worsen the experience for users who rely on adblockers. I could see the EU doing something like this, though I’m not so sure about the US.</p>
<p data-start="1261" data-end="1303">And that’s all I have to say about that...</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>AI will cause mass Unemployment</title>
        <author>
            <name>MrHalfLife</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/ai-will-cause-mass-unemployment.html"/>
        <id>https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/ai-will-cause-mass-unemployment.html</id>

        <updated>2025-06-03T17:55:01+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hello, Today I've compiled a list of Jobs and Careers that will be effected by AI. Why I think so: Here's the image:
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Hello,</p>
<p>Today I've compiled a list of Jobs and Careers that will be effected by AI.</p>
<p>Why I think so:</p>
<ul>
<li>FAANG/Tech Jobs/Programming: AI is actually very good with Programming, and some companies are laying off hard workers with AI</li>
<li>Teachers: There is a school in texas called "Alpha School" where for 2 hours, they are being taught, with no teachers, just access to AI. Which puts teachers, people who have studied one or two subjects for almost their entire lifes, just to be replaced by AI</li>
<li>Musicians: There are programs, that let you create beats or even entire songs using AI. And as an artist, I am very offended.</li>
<li>Banking Systems: This kind of goes into the first one, but they will use more AI for banking stuff</li>
<li>Writing: There could be an episode of a show written entirely by AI, only if the AI knows what happened in the season, or who the characters are with their backstories.</li>
<li>Cashiers: I can see how there won't be any human cashiers, just all AI. At Kaufland, where they have scanners, and if you buy something from the bakery, you go to these weird PC things to scan them without any humans.</li>
<li>Meme Making: Take Italian Brainrot for example, the audio and the picture was made by AI, and it will effect Gen Alpha as a whole</li>
<li>YouTube Videos/Streamers/Filmmaking/Animations: Google showed off their Veo 3 or something, that makes real ass footage. Not only Fortnite gameplay, but Streamers</li>
<li>Artist: AI art is just miserable. On Discord, there was this bot added, called Domo AI, that steals art from a channel for arts, to train a model.</li>
</ul>
<p>Here's the image:</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/media/posts/9/Unemployment-V1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" sizes="(min-width: 920px) 703px, (min-width: 700px) calc(82vw - 35px), calc(100vw - 81px)" srcset="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/media/posts/9/responsive/Unemployment-V1-xs.jpg 300w ,https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/media/posts/9/responsive/Unemployment-V1-sm.jpg 480w ,https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/media/posts/9/responsive/Unemployment-V1-md.jpg 768w ,https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/media/posts/9/responsive/Unemployment-V1-lg.jpg 1024w"></figure>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>When losers have lost their minds (Bigots)</title>
        <author>
            <name>MrHalfLife</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/when-losers-have-lost-their-minds-bigots.html"/>
        <id>https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/when-losers-have-lost-their-minds-bigots.html</id>

        <updated>2025-05-15T18:22:01+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    As you probably know, there's a lot of transphobia, homophobia, right-wing rhetoric, and anti-feminism—especially in the United States, but also to some extent in Germany.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="" data-start="123" data-end="519">As you probably know, there's a lot of transphobia, homophobia, right-wing rhetoric, and anti-feminism—especially in the United States, but also to some extent in Germany. There's been a lot of talk about the AfD, the Trump administration, and some weird multi-billionaire who just wants to destroy U.S. aid. I like to call them <strong data-start="452" data-end="475">"The Three Losers."</strong> Here are my opinions on these three idiots:</p>
<h3 class="" data-start="526" data-end="533">AfD</h3>
<p class="" data-start="535" data-end="1043">The AfD (<em data-start="544" data-end="573">Alternative für Deutschland</em>, or Alternative for Germany) is a right-wing party that was formed in 2013, and honestly, I don’t think I need to explain much further why they’re bad. They’ve been labeled as “certainly right-wing extremist” by the <em data-start="790" data-end="823">Bundesamt für Verfassungsschutz</em> (BfV). They've gained a lot of support in states like Saxony, and even in Thuringia, they've been elected. In the city where I live, the AfD received a lot of votes—though not enough to actually govern the state I’m in.</p>
<h3 class="" data-start="1050" data-end="1074">Trump Administration</h3>
<p class="" data-start="1076" data-end="1593">Donald Trump was elected president in 2016, and again in 2025. During his time as president of the United <em data-start="1182" data-end="1191">Fucking</em> States of America, he's made decisions that completely confuse me. For example, in 2025, Trump banned transgender military members from serving in the U.S. military, stating there are “only two genders,” which is completely false. Back in 2020, even Krist Novoselic—yes, <strong data-start="1463" data-end="1486">THE Krist Novoselic</strong>—got hate for supporting Trump. I mean, what do you expect from a former bassist being a politician?</p>
<p class="" data-start="1595" data-end="2055">Then there are the U.S. tech companies like Google, which reportedly removed Pride Month from Google Maps entirely, and even renamed the Gulf of Mexico to the “Gulf of America.” Out of all the issues facing the United States, <em data-start="1821" data-end="1827">this</em> is what they chose to focus on? I think you folks in the U.S. are probably more informed than I am, since I live in Germany and get most of my U.S. news online—so maybe I shouldn't believe everything. But still, it’s messed up.</p>
<p class="" data-start="2057" data-end="2101">And speaking of messed up… that leads us to:</p>
<h3 class="" data-start="2108" data-end="2141">Elon Musk (Multi-Billionaire)</h3>
<p class="" data-start="2143" data-end="2449">Before he bought Twitter and basically did a gesture resembling a Hitler salute, I thought he was a pretty cool guy. He came off as a billionaire who didn’t take himself too seriously. But after diving headfirst into MAGA culture and promoting DOGE, I’ve decided there’s nothing good left to say about him.</p>
<p class="" data-start="2451" data-end="2924">Not only does he seem to have an administration in the U.S. full of teenagers and unqualified hires, firing actual government employees, but he also wants to dismantle the Department of Education and eliminate U.S. Aid programs. What even goes on in his brain? Why target the Department of Education? Does he want future kids to grow up with nothing but an iPad shoved in their faces and no real education? And why cut U.S. Aid? You don’t want treatment for AIDS or cancer?</p>
<p class="" data-start="2926" data-end="2964">Also—<strong data-start="2931" data-end="2964">I WANT THE FUCKING BIRD BACK!</strong></p>
<p class="" data-start="2966" data-end="3189">And as for him calling one of his kids, Vivian Jenna Wilson, a victim of the “woke mind virus”—basically calling being transgender a virus—what the hell? Didn’t he literally sign the papers for her transition? Like, <em data-start="3182" data-end="3188">what</em>?</p>
<p class="" data-start="3196" data-end="3224">Yes, the world is cooked. 😭</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Quick rant about italian brainrot</title>
        <author>
            <name>MrHalfLife</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/quick-rant-about-italian-brainrot.html"/>
        <id>https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/quick-rant-about-italian-brainrot.html</id>

        <updated>2025-05-14T19:32:38+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    [warning: rant] WHY DO VIDEOS WITH BARELY ANY EFFORT GET 100 MILLION VIEWS. IT WILL DIE IN LIKE 2 TO 3 MONTHS AND EVERYBODY WOULD&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>[warning: rant]</p>
<p>WHY DO VIDEOS WITH BARELY ANY EFFORT GET 100 MILLION VIEWS. IT WILL DIE IN LIKE 2 TO 3 MONTHS AND EVERYBODY WOULD FORGET!</p>
<p>DOES ANYONE KNOW WHAT "Bombarido Crocodilo" MEANS??? HERE'S THE TRANSLATION</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Bombarido Crocodilo, a fucking flying alligator that flies and bombs children in Gaza and Palestine, doesn't believe in Allah and loves bombs. It feeds on the spirit of your mother. And if you translated all of this, then you're an asshole. Don't break the joke. Whore.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>HOW CAN YOU SUPPORT STUFF, WHEN IT SAYS THAT DOESN'T BELIEVE IN ALLAH, AND BOMBING KIDS IN GAZA AND PALESTINE!</p>
<p>This shit needs to die....</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What were the &quot;Halloween Documents&quot;</title>
        <author>
            <name>MrHalfLife</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/what-were-the-halloween-documents.html"/>
        <id>https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/what-were-the-halloween-documents.html</id>

        <updated>2025-05-01T12:26:15+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    The Halloween documents are a series of secret Microsoft memos from the late 1990s. They came to light because they were leaked by a Microsoft&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The Halloween documents are a series of secret Microsoft memos from the late 1990s. They came to light because they were leaked by a Microsoft employee and published by open source advocate Eric S. Raymond - many of them around October 31, hence the name.<br><br>The documents show: Microsoft saw Linux and open source software as a serious threat and developed strategies to slow their success - despite public statements to the contrary.</p>
<table class="wikitable sortable jquery-tablesorter">
<thead>
<tr>
<th class="headerSort" tabindex="0" title="Sort ascending" role="columnheader button">No.</th>
<th class="headerSort" tabindex="0" title="Sort ascending" role="columnheader button">Name</th>
<th class="headerSort" tabindex="0" title="Sort ascending" role="columnheader button">Author</th>
<th class="headerSort" tabindex="0" title="Sort ascending" role="columnheader button">Date</th>
<th class="headerSort" tabindex="0" title="Sort ascending" role="columnheader button">Brief description</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr valign="top">
<td>I</td>
<td>"Open Source Software: A (New?) Development Methodology"</td>
<td>Microsoft / Vinod Valloppillil</td>
<td><span data-sort-value="000000001998-08-01-0000">August 1998</span></td>
<td>A leaked internal report <sup id="cite_ref-document1_1-3" class="reference"></sup></td>
</tr>
<tr valign="top">
<td>II</td>
<td>"Linux OS Competitive Analysis: The Next Java VM?"</td>
<td>Microsoft / Vinod Valloppillil</td>
<td><span data-sort-value="000000001998-08-01-0000">August 1998</span></td>
<td>A leaked internal report <sup id="cite_ref-document2_4-0" class="reference"></sup></td>
</tr>
<tr valign="top">
<td>III</td>
<td>Untitled statement</td>
<td>Microsoft / Aurelia van den Berg</td>
<td><span data-sort-value="000000001998-11-01-0000">November 1998</span></td>
<td>Press statement from Microsoft Netherlands <sup id="cite_ref-document3_5-0" class="reference"></sup></td>
</tr>
<tr valign="top">
<td>IV</td>
<td>"When Software Things Were Rotten"</td>
<td>Eric S. Raymond</td>
<td><span data-sort-value="000000001998-12-01-0000">December 1998</span></td>
<td>A satire piece based on Microsoft's <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/w/index.php?title=Ed_Muth&amp;action=edit&amp;redlink=1" class="new" title="Ed Muth (page does not exist)">Ed Muth</a> comparing open source developers to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robin_Hood" title="Robin Hood">Robin Hood</a>.</td>
</tr>
<tr valign="top">
<td>V</td>
<td>"The FUD Begins"</td>
<td>Eric S. Raymond</td>
<td><span data-sort-value="000000001999-03-01-0000">March 1999</span></td>
<td>A response by Raymond to Ed Muth's allegations that Linux has a "weak <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Value_proposition" title="Value proposition">value proposition</a>".</td>
</tr>
<tr valign="top">
<td>VI</td>
<td>"The Fatal Anniversary"</td>
<td>Eric S. Raymond</td>
<td><span data-sort-value="000000001999-10-01-0000">October 1999</span></td>
<td>A response by Raymond to studies authored by the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gartner" title="Gartner">Gartner</a> group for Microsoft.</td>
</tr>
<tr valign="top">
<td>VII</td>
<td>"Research E-Bulletin: Attitudes Towards Shared Source and Open Source Research Study"</td>
<td>Microsoft</td>
<td><span data-sort-value="000000002002-09-01-0000">September 2002</span></td>
<td>A summary of the results of a Microsoft survey describing reactions to Microsoft's <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shared_Source_Initiative" title="Shared Source Initiative">Shared Source Initiative</a>.</td>
</tr>
<tr valign="top">
<td>VIII</td>
<td>"OSS and Government"</td>
<td>Microsoft / Orlando Ayala</td>
<td><span data-sort-value="000000002002-11-01-0000">November 2002</span></td>
<td>Describes Microsoft's procedures for responding to notable conversions away from Microsoft software </td>
</tr>
<tr valign="top">
<td>IX</td>
<td>"It Ain't Necessarily SCO"</td>
<td>Eric S. Raymond and Rob Landley</td>
<td><span data-sort-value="000000002003-08-01-0000">August 2003</span></td>
<td>A response to the allegations made by the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SCO_Group" title="SCO Group">SCO Group</a> in its initial filings in <i><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SCO_v._IBM" class="mw-redirect" title="SCO v. IBM">SCO v. IBM</a></i>.<sup id="cite_ref-document9_11-0" class="reference"></sup></td>
</tr>
<tr valign="top">
<td>X</td>
<td>"Follow The Money"</td>
<td>Mike Anderer</td>
<td><span data-sort-value="000000002004-03-01-0000">March 2004</span></td>
<td>An e-mail from consultant Mike Anderer to SCO's Chris Sontag revealing Microsoft's channeling of $86<span class="nowrap"> </span>million (equivalent to $140<span class="nowrap"> </span>million in 2024) to SCO.<sup id="cite_ref-document10_12-0" class="reference"></sup></td>
</tr>
<tr valign="top">
<td>XI</td>
<td>"Get The FUD"</td>
<td>Eric S. Raymond</td>
<td><span data-sort-value="000000002004-06-01-0000">June 2004</span></td>
<td>A response to Microsoft's "<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Get_the_Facts" class="mw-redirect" title="Get the Facts">Get the Facts</a>" campaign <sup id="cite_ref-document11_13-0" class="reference"></sup></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p class="" data-start="94" data-end="236"><strong data-start="94" data-end="116">Documents I and II</strong><br data-start="116" data-end="119">These are leaked reports for Microsoft's own use, both written by Vinod Valloppillil, a program manager at Microsoft.</p>
<p class="" data-start="238" data-end="558">Document I provides a detailed introduction to the concepts behind open source software and its possible impact on Microsoft products and services. It outlines the strengths and weaknesses of open source software. Document II describes the basic architecture of the Linux system, and its relation to Unix and Windows NT.</p>
<p class="" data-start="560" data-end="1025">Document I revealed that "FUD" (spreading fear, uncertainty, and doubt) was a traditional Microsoft marketing strategy, acknowledged and understood internally. Examples of Microsoft's FUD tactics are announcing nonexistent products or spreading rumors that competing products will crash Windows. Raymond suggests that the documents show that while Microsoft may have been dismissive of open source software in public, it privately considers it a serious competitor.</p>
<p class="" data-start="1027" data-end="1727">In discussing ways of competing with open source, Document I suggests that one reason that open source projects had been able to enter the server market is the market's use of standardized protocols. The document then suggests that this can be stopped by "extending these protocols and developing new protocols" and "de-commoditiz[ing] protocols &amp; applications". This policy has been internally nicknamed "embrace, extend, extinguish". Document I also suggests that open source software "is long-term credible ... FUD tactics can not be used to combat it", and "Recent case studies (the Internet) provide very dramatic evidence ... that commercial quality can be achieved / exceeded by OSS projects."</p>
<p class="" data-start="1729" data-end="1826">Documents I and II were filed as evidence on January 16, 2007, in the case of Comes v. Microsoft.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The main problems with YouTube Revivals</title>
        <author>
            <name>MrHalfLife</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/the-main-problems-with-youtube-revivals.html"/>
        <id>https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/the-main-problems-with-youtube-revivals.html</id>

        <updated>2025-03-30T12:00:26+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hello, So, as you know, I used to have a BitView account, and currently own a KamTape and EraCast account. My BitView account got banned,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Hello,<br><br>So, as you know, I used to have a BitView account, and currently own a KamTape and EraCast account. My BitView account got banned, if you wanna read the reason, look at the post "About the whole BitView stuff".<br><br>The problem is that the moderation of most of the Revivals sucks, you can find music videos on BitView from big artists like Madonna (which I reported), I like the way that EraCast handles Copyright, they have a Content-ID-like feature where if you upload copyrighted material, it will be auto-flagged.<br><br>Another problem is the Trolls, there will be these disgusting pieces of crap on these sites and so.<br><br>But the mods are really nice, and I have met multiple nice people on these revivals, like A Treeager.<br><br>And that's all I have to say about that</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>About the whole BitView stuff</title>
        <author>
            <name>MrHalfLife</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/about-the-whole-bitview-stuff.html"/>
        <id>https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/about-the-whole-bitview-stuff.html</id>

        <updated>2025-03-26T18:31:21+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hello (this is a repost, og post here) I know this situation is like 21 days old as I am writing this (the whole stuff&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Hello (this is a repost, og post <a href="https://blog.spacehey.com/entry?id=1440880">here</a>)</p>
<p>I know this situation is like 21 days old as I am writing this (the whole stuff happened at 2.2.2025)</p>
<p>This response won't start with "I made a severe and continuous lapse in my judgment, and I don’t expect to be forgiven. I’m simply here to apologize."</p>
<p>So, yes, I got banned from BitView, I know it sucks and it sucks for me too. Well, I had this idea for a response for a while now but didn't see the time until now.</p>
<p>Around the 2nd of February, when news broke out that ATreeager got banned from BitView, similar to what happened on the 31st of December 2024, with the whole Wizz thing. The Treeager Trashtalk server got many members basically trying to figure out what the hell was going on. I won't get too much into detail, since one of BitView mods made a blog post that you can read here:<br>https://www.bitview.net/blog#169</p>
<p>I was also confused with all the other BitView people, the chat was going insane, and also the day before, ATreeager's server was raided by trolls and so on.</p>
<p>Now this may seem like I just mention here for no reason in the middle of this blog, but my brain sometimes makes random sentences that could seem offensive without a second thought, but when confronted or looking back, I may say "Who is this idiot" or "oh shit, here come the consequences".</p>
<p>I made a very <strong>BAD </strong>comment about a BitView moderator/maintainer, during a time when messages like "Bittoco is evil" and so were sent. I've heard someone from the Bittoco Discord Server was sending the convos from Treeager's server there, and since they posted it there, it was seen as Transphobic. I know I have responsibility for the stuff I say online or offline, and it ended up adding more fuel to the fire, since now the topic of transphobia is now in this situation about grooming and so</p>
<p>I was banned 30 minutes later from BitView and the Bittoco Discord Server permanently.</p>
<p>I panicked, it was also around 9 p.m. or 10 p.m. when I started to think of what I was banned for, since Carlbot just N/A, so no ban reason for me.</p>
<p>Someone said to contact a BitView mod on Discord, which I did. I had a convo with them for 28 minutes, until they ended up saying "Yeah I'll send it to the staff and see what they think."</p>
<p>I also do want to talk about something, that the BitView mod probably noticed (and the staff if they sent it to them)</p>
<p>The time that took for me to respond was suspiciously slow as if I was trying to make excuses to get me back to the platform, which has been used many times with bad people. I asked myself, things like "Why did you write this", "What was your motive" and other stuff, and it takes way too much time to actually get an answer if you are asking yourself. Some people may relate. But another reason why it took so slowly is because I was tired as hell and I needed to complete to talk to the BitView staff before going to bed</p>
<p>If any BitView staff is reading this to the end, great! You have heard my side of the story, but I do have another thing: If I make a stupid comment, say something stupid, or just begin in a bad day, someone, that is either a BitView staff or so, could ask me "Hey MrHalfLife, are you good?" or "Hey MrHalfLife, what did you mean with that comment?" etc. I may say "I am in a bad day" or I may say the word "Brainmesser" which means in this context "Yeah, I made a statement without second thoughts." which could be really good.<br><br>So, I'm sorry for anyone who got offended. I am just some 13 year old who just didn't think before sending a message.</p>
<p>And that's all I have to say about that...<br><br><strong>EDIT (16.03.2025)</strong>: BitView changed their age requirement from 13 to 14+, and since I am turning 14 this year, on the 8th of December, I may come back. However I am not sure if the Bittoco people or BitView people would read this</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Welcome to HalfBlog</title>
        <author>
            <name>MrHalfLife</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/welcome-to-halfblog.html"/>
        <id>https://mrhalflife280.github.io/HalfBlog/welcome-to-halfblog.html</id>

        <updated>2025-03-23T16:01:50+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hello, this is my new blog, for real this time, I won’t be using ATSPACE with WordPress since it needs SSL, which you have to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Hello, this is my new blog, for real this time, I won’t be using ATSPACE with WordPress since it needs SSL, which you have to pay for :(</p><p>So I decided to post the blog posts here, hosted under GitHub Pages!</p><p>End.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
